https://www.eminitradingstrategies.com/policies.html

EMINI TRADING STRATEGIES PRIVACY POLICY AND CONTACT INFORMATION
MemberLogin
"The Tick Trader"
About David Marsh
Email David Marsh
Privacy Policy - Contact and Support
ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY AGREEMENT
Traders Education, LLC, is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.
THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to Traders Education, LLC, and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of www.eminitradingstrategies.com you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.
Collection of Information
This website collects various types of information, such as:
Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs.
We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.
It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information collected.
Use of Information Collected
Traders Education, LLC may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from www.eminitradingstrategies.com. Traders Education, LLC
may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.
Traders Education, LLC does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.
Traders Education, LLC may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to gleam what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public.
Traders Education, LLC may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:
Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Traders Education, LLC and/or our website;
Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Traders Education, LLC; and
Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of www.eminitradingstrategies.com and/or the general public.
Children Under Age of 13
Traders Education, LLC does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system's database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.
Unsubscribe or Opt-Out
All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to info@eminitradingstrategies.com. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. Traders Education, LLC does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.
Security
Traders Education, LLC shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user's personal information under our control.
The company also uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for authentication and private communications in an effort to build users' trust and confidence in the internet and website use by providing simple and secure access and communication of credit card and personal information.
The website is also secured by VeriSign.
Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement
Traders Education, LLC reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those change to our website homepage at www.eminitradingstrategies.com, so that our users and/or visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point in time Traders Education, LLC decides to make use of any personally identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate manner.
Acceptance of Terms
Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the following email, telephone number or mailing address.
Email: info@eminitradingstrategies.com
Telephone Number: (904) 342-3221
Mailing Address:
Traders Education, LLC
10030 EW Pappy Road, STE 9
Saint Johns, Florida 32259
CONTACT AND SUPPORT
www.eminitradingstrategies.com is owned by Traders Education LLC
Sales/Support: al@eminitradingstrategies.com
Software/Corporate: rick@eminitradingstrategies.com
Trading Course/Training: david@eminitradingstrategies.com
Student Services/Administration: monica@eminitradingstrategies.com
Billing and support provided by:
Traders Education LLC
10030 EW Pappy Road
Suite 9
Saint Johns, FL 32259
Phone: 904-342-3221
Fax: 904-212-0899
info@eminitradingstrategies.com
Important:
To avoid the possibility that email correspondence from us will not be accepted by your email program, please add "*@eminitradingstrategies.com" to your Contacts and whitelist in your email program. Some email programs have not been noticing our emails as legitimate and sending them to the recipient's spam folders.
Thank you, David.
Home
BreakoutPullback
PTS Indicator
PTS TraderStrategy
NinjaTrader
AutomatedTrading
BeginnersInfo
Pricing
Small Business Websites by Xisle Graphix
Important Notice - Risk Disclaimer:
Notice/Warning: This notice cannot and does not disclose or explain all of the risks and other significant aspects involved in trading FUTURES, but you should particularly note the following:
Under margin trading conditions even small market movements may have great impact on the customer's trading account. You must consider that if the market moves against you, you may sustain a total loss greater than the funds deposited. You are responsible for all the risks and financial resources you use and for the chosen trading system. It is important that you should not engage in trading unless you understand the nature of the transaction you are entering into and, the true extent of the exposure to the risk of loss.
This product may not be suitable for all investors; therefore if you do not fully understand the risks involved, you must seek independent advice. All trading strategies are to be used at your own risk.
Traders Education LLC is not responsible for any losses incurred as a result of using any of our trading strategies/software.
The AutoTrader software should never be left unattended due to many variables outside of your control such as computer or data failure, power outages, position mismatches, network problems, etc.
Past performance is no guarantee of future returns. This software should not be relied upon as advice or construed as a recommendation of any kind.
It is your responsibility to confirm and decide which trades to take. Trade at your own risk.
Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) Rule 4.41
HYPOTHETICAL PERFORMANCE RESULTS HAVE MANY INHERENT LIMITATIONS, SOME OF WHICH ARE DESCRIBED BELOW. NO REPRESENTATION IS BEING MADE THAT ANY ACCOUNT WILL OR IS LIKELY TO ACHIEVE PROFITS OR LOSSES SIMILAR TO THOSE SHOWN; IN FACT, THERE ARE FREQUENTLY SHARP DIFFERENCES BETWEEN HYPOTHETICAL PERFORMANCE RESULTS AND THE ACTUAL RESULTS SUBSEQUENTLY ACHIEVED BY ANY PARTICULAR TRADING PROGRAM. ONE OF THE LIMITATIONS OF HYPOTHETICAL PERFORMANCE RESULTS IS THAT THEY ARE GENERALLY PREPARED WITH THE BENEFIT OF HINDSIGHT. IN ADDITION, HYPOTHETICAL TRADING DOES NOT INVOLVE FINANCIAL RISK, AND NO HYPOTHETICAL TRADING RECORD CAN COMPLETELY ACCOUNT FOR THE IMPACT OF FINANCIAL RISK OF ACTUAL TRADING. FOR EXAMPLE, THE ABILITY TO WITHSTAND LOSSES OR TO ADHERE TO A PARTICULAR TRADING PROGRAM IN SPITE OF TRADING LOSSES ARE MATERIAL POINTS WHICH CAN ALSO ADVERSELY AFFECT ACTUAL TRADING RESULTS. THERE ARE NUMEROUS OTHER FACTORS RELATED TO THE MARKETS IN GENERAL OR TO THE IMPLEMENTATION OF ANY SPECIFIC TRADING PROGRAM WHICH CANNOT BE FULLY ACCOUNTED FOR IN THE PREPARATION OF HYPOTHETICAL PERFORMANCE RESULTS AND ALL WHICH CAN ADVERSELY AFFECT TRADING RESULTS. THESE PERFORMANCE TABLES AND RESULTS ARE HYPOTHETICAL IN NATURE AND DO NOT REPRESENT TRADING IN ACTUAL ACCOUNTS.
